For your courage. For your love. For your sacrifice.
Thank You for Your Service is a drama, war film directed by Jason Hall.
A group of U.S.
soldiers returning from Iraq struggle to integrate back into family and civilian life, while living with
the memory of a war that threatens to destroy them long after they've left the battlefield.
Adam Schumann, played by Miles Teller.
Saskia Schumann, played by Haley Bennett.
Billy Waller, played by Joe Cole.
Amanda Doster, played by Amy Schumer.
Tausolo "Solo" Aieti, played by Beulah Koale.
Michael Adam Emory, played by Scott Haze.
Thank You for Your Service is a 2017 American biographical war drama film written and directed by Jason Hall, in
his directorial debut, and based on the 2013 non-fiction book of the same name by David Finkel.
Finkel, a Washington Post reporter, wrote about veterans of the 2nd Battalion, 16th Infantry Regiment
returning to the vicinity of Fort Riley, Kansas, following a 15-month deployment in Iraq in 2007.
The film is about posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD), depicting U.S.
soldiers who try to adjust to civilian life, and stars Miles Teller,
Haley Bennett, Beulah Koale, Amy Schumer, and Scott Haze.
Bruce Springsteen wrote the song "Freedom Cadence"
specifically for the closing credits.
The film had its world premiere at the Heartland Film Festival on October 15, 2017, and was
theatrically released in the United States on October 27, 2017, by Universal Pictures.
It received generally positive reviews, with praise for Teller's performance,
but grossed just $9 million against its $20 million budget.
The film explores themes of post-traumatic stress disorder (ptsd),
based on novel or book, biography, soldier, military.
The tone is emotional.